我想到一个方法能让我值得为你花时间和精力
I figured out a way to make you worth my time.
25%
25%.
我要你从这条街上赚取的所有收益的25%
Everything that you take off the street.
看来我也没得选
It doesn't look like I have a choice.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
这样我良心不安
I don't want that on my conscience.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
这小子说得对  不是今晚
The kid's right, man, not tonight.
我不是那种破坏别人家庭的人
I'm not a home wrecker.
就当什么都没发生过吧
What happened never happened.
恭喜你  阿特沃特  欢迎加入情报组
Congratulations, Atwater. You just made Intelligence.
-我能问下为什么吗  -为什么不选你吗
- Can I ask why? - You didn't make the cut?
我不欣赏办公室恋情
I don't tolerate in-house romance.
听着  你有个儿子  查理  安妮生的
Listen, you've got a son, Charlie, with Annie.
原本的交易是我带你进来
The deal was I take you in,
-他就得远离伊利诺斯州  -我会处理的
- he stays out of Illinois. - I will handle it.
我被迫夹着尾巴做人
I got flushed down the toilet,
就为了让你当警察
so you could play cop.
-你得帮我  -当然
- You owe me. - Sure.
很好
Good answer.
你完全可以去找我
You had every opportunity to reach out to me.
完全可以  可你没有
Every opportunity, you shut me out!
-住手  -艾琳
- Stop! - Erin!
她没事
She's fine!
没事
She's fine.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you okay? - Yes.
你会后悔踏进芝加哥的  查理
You're gonna wish you'd stayed out of Chicago, Charlie.
不  是你会后悔
No, what you're gonna wish
我没忘记桑多瓦尔的事
is that I'd forgotten all about Sandoval.
我记得清清楚楚
But I haven't, have I?
你想抓我吗  尽管来啊
You want to take me in? Let's go.
我很乐意告诉大家当时发生的事
I'm happy to tell everyone what happened,
如果没记错  就在离这里不到五条街的地方
not five streets from here, if I recall.
或者  我有办法了
Or, hey, I got an idea.
我们不要纠结过去了
Instead of the past,
多关注一下将来吧
why don't we focus on the future?
好
Sure.
你想要什么  多少
What do you want? How much?
就凭你警察那点工资可远远不够
More than you can afford on a cop's salary.
这个得需要以前那个琳德赛
I'm gonna need the old Lindsay for this one.
你简直疯了
You're out of your mind.
是吗  我以前一直做好人
Really? You know, I played nice guy before
帮你们两个守着秘密
and kept my mouth shut for you two.
可到头来我得到了什么
What did it get me?
我一个人在外漂泊了12年
12 years wandering the wilderness
你却在这里当警察  而你养大了我儿子
while you got to play cop and you raised my son!
不准碰她
Don't touch her!
这次先算了
Nah, not this time.
你乖乖听话  否则我就让天下人都知道
I'm getting my payday, or I run my mouth.
我今天就要
I need that today.
求你了  艾琳
Please, Erin.
-安妮  -艾琳  求你了
- Annie... - Erin, please...
不管他要什么  你...
Whatever he needs, just--
你就给他吧
Just give it to him.
汉克
Hank.
我拿到钱了你才能拿到
You get paid when I get paid.
我就这样等着  就这样相信你的话吗
I'm supposed to wait around, take your word for it?
对
That's right.
-你要想搞鬼...  -你已经说过了
- You try and screw me-- - You already told me already.
我知道你有办法整我  我也有
You got bear traps set up. Well, so do I.
这叫什么来着  相互确保摧毁对吧
What's it called-- mutually assured destruction?
我们还是不要走到那一步为好
How about we avoid all that?
别急  等着你那份儿就行
You just relax and wait for your cut.
好
Yeah.
早啊
Hey. Good morning.
早
Yeah. Morning.
阿特沃特
Atwater, hey.
-早  -早上好
- Hey. - Good morning.
兄弟  你用萨姆纳的桌子
Here, man, take Sumner's desk.
-你好  兄弟  -你好
- What's up, man? - What's up, bro?
不要太习惯用办公桌
Don't get used it to it, though.
反正我们桌前办公的时间也不多
We don't seem to stay in them for very long.
伯吉斯怎么样了
How is Burgess taking it?
什么怎么样
Taking what?
你升职进情报组了
You know, you getting promoted up here,
可是...
when perhaps...
或许她比你更合适一点
she deserves it a little bit more.
这个啊
Oh, that.
她现在都有新搭档了
Well, she's been assigned a new partner.
他回来了
There he is.
哥们  你怎么这么早就回来上班了
Hey, man, what the hell you doing back so soon, huh?
各位  你们怎么跟我老婆似的
Oh, guys. You sound like my wife.
听我说  我们给你
Listen, we got you
准备了一件欢迎回来
a little "welcome back/
也就是恭喜你没死的礼物
glad you're not dead" gift.
可别说我们不爱你
Don't say we didn't ever do anything for you.
太搞笑了
That's hilarious.
来  靠近点
Come here, a little closer.
是他的主意
His idea.
你想过几招吗
Oh, you want some of this?
-就是我的主意  -我看未必
- It was my idea. - I didn't think so.
没事吧
You okay?
好  我们五分钟后...马上出发
All right, we're rolling out...five minutes.
有大案子
We just caught a heater.
-很高兴你回来了  兄弟  -谢谢
- Glad you're back, bro. - Thanks.
帮我个忙
Hey, do me a favor.
你先在办公室工作几天吧
Just work the desk for a few days.
我不想你在我手下出事
I don't want you dropping on me.
我没事  马上去换衣服
I'm fine. I'm suiting up.
安东尼奥  这事儿没得商量
Antonio, I'm not gonna argue with you about this.
好吧
All right.
他们是有计划有组织的
They had a plan.
他们把这片区域内的监控摄像头都弄走了
They took out all the security cameras in the area.
吉恩查过那边监控了  什么也没有
Jin checked the PODS. There's nothing there.
丢失了100磅
They're missing 100 pounds
镀铝水胶炸药
of aluminized water-gel explosives.
-水胶  -那是开矿和挖隧道用的
- Water gels? - It's for mining and tunneling.
公司会用它对基岩进行爆破
Companies use it for blasting bedrock.
是啊  炸药量可不小
Yeah, that's a lot of explosives,
都能炸垮一栋大楼了
like take-down-a-building big.
最近爆炸案已经够多的了
We've had enough of that around here.
老大  还有个保安不见了
They're also missing a security guard, boss.
好吧  给我一份名单
All right, I want a list
上面要有爆破公司所有员工
of all the demo-company employees
还有所有来签收过物料的人的资料
and whoever signed for the materials here.
所有知道水胶炸弹的人
Anyone who knew water-gel explosives
都可能到过现场
were gonna be on site.
这边
Over here!
什么情况
What's this?
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
好吧  我要知道最近一个月到过这里的
All right, anyone who's been here in the last month,
所有人的名字
I want their name.
我得挂了
Gotta go.
吉恩
Hey, Jin.
早上好  艾琳
Good morning, Erin.
我想找你帮个忙
I need a favor...
私下的
Off the books.
早习惯了
Isn't it always?
你进得去城市规划分区委员会吗
Do you have access to the city planning and zoning commission?
你要什么
Uh... as in?
他们的规划图
Blueprints.
可以
Yes.
要神不知鬼不觉
Without anybody knowing.
你老婆打电话来了
Your wife called.
想和你讨论一下晚餐的事
Wants to know about dinner.
鲁塞克  你的冰箱周四送到
Ruzek, your fridge is getting delivered on Thursday.
终于来了
Ah, finally.
是九到十二点还是三到六点
Between 9:00 and 12:00 or 3:00 and 6:00?
他们说了吗
Did they say?
算了  没事
Never mind.
警长  我们不如请个市民来帮忙接电话
Hey, Sarge. Why don't we have a civilian aide up here taking calls?
预算里反正有这项
It's in the budget.
随便来个人我们信不过  安东尼奥
It's all about who you can trust, Antonio.
你查到什么了
What do you got?
我在等一份
I'm waiting on a list
建筑工地所有员工信息的名单
of employees from that construction site.
迄今为止  没有可疑的人
So far, no one's popped.
你之前说他们没有
And you said they didn't get
雷管或导火线之类的对吗
any blasting caps or detonation cords?
是的
No.
要用炸药肯定得用这些
You're gonna need those.
好吧  雷管和导火索
All right, det cords and caps--
我们先从这个开始查吧
That's our angle for now.
我有个线人  我可以去问问他
I got a C.I. I can talk to about that.
好
All right.
警长
Yo, Sarge.
怎么了
Yeah?
我小时候是在哈维长大的
You know, I grew up in Harvey,
就在那个建筑工地旁边
right there near the construction site.
那是二八党的地盘
That's Two-eights territory.
那里的一切都和他们脱不了干系
Nothing goes down there without their permission.
我认识个人
I know a guy.
我可以去打听打听消息
I think I can lean on him a little bit, see what he knows.
奥林斯基
Olinsky...
跟他一起去
Go with him.
我自己来就行了  老奥
Actually, I think I'm gonna do this by myself, O.
大家注意一下
Oh, hey, everyone,
阿特沃特刚来这个队还没两分钟呢
Atwater's been in the unit two minutes,
就把自己当个主事儿人了
and already he's put himself in charge.
祝贺你了  兄弟
Congrats, bud.
我就知道你是个管理人才
I knew you were management material.
不不不  我不是这个意思
Oh, no, no, that's not what I was trying to say.
那你是什么意思
What were you saying?
其实是...
It's just--
你是怕你的白人搭档
Oh, you're worried about your white-cop partner
把这事儿弄砸了吗
blowing the deal?
是啊
Yeah.
我当了20年的卧底了
Maybe after 20 years working undercover,
知道怎么掩藏自己的身份
I know how not to get made...
在芝加哥难不倒我
anywhere in the city.
不好意思
My bad.
安东尼奥  能帮我个忙吗
Antonio, I need a solid.
行啊
Yeah, sure.
好吧
All right.
你还记得娜迪亚吗
You remember Nadia?
她在穆尼奥斯和伯吉斯那件事上帮过我们
She helped us out back with Munoz and Burgess.
娜迪亚  对  我记得
Nadia? Oh, yeah, yeah, I remember Nadia.
她今天出康复中心
Okay. She's getting out of rehab today.
我本来该去接她的
I'm supposed to pick her up.
千万别跟我说你想让我去...
Please don't tell me you're gonna ask me to--
老兄  我是认真的
Dude, I'm serious.
今天别开玩笑  帮我个忙
Not today. I need some help.
没问题  地址呢
No sweat. What's the address?
谢谢
Thank you.
就让她待在这  好吗
Just keep her up here, all right?
在我下班带她回家之前
I don't want her going anywhere
我不想让她四处乱跑
until I can take her home after shift.
收到
Copy that.
好冷啊
It's cold.
怎么了  霍斯特德
What's up, Halstead?
-你这朋友叫什么  -鲁塞克  这是慕斯
- Who's your friend? - Ruzek. Ruzek, Mouse.
你好  伙计
What's up, man?
-吃点薯条吧  -听着
- Have some fries. - Hey, listen...
哈维那边工地上
Can you tell me anything
发生了抢劫案  你知道什么消息吗
about this construction-site robbery in Harvey?
-这可不好说  -是吗
- I might be tapped in on that. - Yeah?
都怪我的耳朵  伙计
It's my ears, man.
最近耳屎有点多啊
They get so waxy these days.
是啊  最近耳屎多
Oh, yeah, so waxy these days, yeah--
他的耳朵  呵呵
His ears, yeah.
这就对了嘛
Yeah. Ding-ding.
突然听得一清二楚了呢
Clear as a bell, just like that.
真好用啊
Just like that.
很多人都在说
There's lots of talk.
城里来了个新人物  他想找几个手下
There's this new player in town. He's looking for some bangers.
我差不多算是个顾问吧
I'm kind of serving as a consultant.
你能安排我们见面吧
Can you get us a meeting?
告诉他我们可以提供雷管和导火线
Tell him we're offering blasting caps and det cord.
-你说真的  -真的
- What, straight up? - Yeah, straight up.
你只需要安排我们见面就行了
All you're doing is organizing a meet.
好吧
All right.
朝伊利和塞奇威克方向开
Drive toward Erie and Sedgwick.
-马上  伙计  -我会安排
- Right on, man. - I'll set it up.
AT-AT指挥官
Commander AT-AT.
《星球大战》中步行机甲战车的指挥官
最近怎么样啊
What's good, son?
循规蹈矩  你懂的
Straight and narrow. You know me.
是啊  你一直那么规矩
Yeah. Well, you always were.
一直都是
You always were.
找我什么事
So what's up, man?
你这不是韬光养晦去了吗[原义为罚球]
If only you could shoot free throws straight.
得了吧  我可一直在干活  帮人解决问题呢
Come on, man, I kept people out the paint, didn't I?
没听说过我还得负责得分啊
Nobody told me I had to score too.
还真是
True.
怎么样  伙计  现在在哪个部门
What's up, man? Where the uniform at?
我现在负责大案子了
I'm on to big and better things now.
-我在特别调查组  -是吗
- Special unit. - Yeah?
是啊
Yeah.
看看你
Well, look at you.
-多威风啊  -你懂的
- Look at you. - You know it.
所以有什么事吗
So what's up, man?
我在那个会展中心有门路
You know I got the hookup over there at the convention center.
我可以帮你们搞到批发价的电子产品
I can get you and the crew wholesale electronics
就在电子消费产品展会之后
right after the big C.E. Show.
包括Wii  PS游戏机
I'm talking about wiis, playstations,
均为电子游戏机
你要的一切  都是些好东西
Everything you like, all on the up-and-up.
是吗
Yeah?
我听着呢  然后呢
I'm listening. What's up?
只要你把我介绍给科普兰·布里格斯
Just need you to introduce me to Copeland Briggs.
不行
No way, man.
别这样  老兄
Come on, dog.
我们俩这么铁
You're like my brother, man.
没错
We are.
不过你听好了
But listen, man, let me tell you something.
如果你以为
if you think for one second
几个批发价的WII
that a couple wholesale WIIs
就能让你这个吉祥物一样的傻大个
is gonna get your jolly green giant-looking ass
见到科普兰·布里格斯
into Copeland Briggs,
那你就大错特错了  兄弟
you got another thing coming, brother.
那是什么
Yeah, what's that?
只要你让我跟布里格斯搭上线
You sit me down next to Briggs,
下次被抓的时候你就可以打这个电话
you always got that number next time you get pinched.
你知道这值多少钱
You know how much that's worth.
你要的东西
As requested.
没人知道吧
Nobody knows about this?
-没  -包括你
- Nope. - Not even you?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
德兰尼  普拉特让我们搭档我很高兴
Delaney, I'm glad Platt partnered us up.
我一直都很想
I've been looking forward
和经验丰富的警官一起工作
to working with an experienced officer.
我叫伯吉斯
My name's Burgess.
知道了  我先停这儿了
Yeah, well, I'm gonna park it right here.
你看到什么了吗
Do you see something?
出什么事了吗
Are we onto something?
我只是想让眼睛休息一下
I'm just gonna rest my eyes for a minute.
笑什么
What is it?
伯吉斯发来的  她的搭档是个睡美人
Uh, Burgess. She got a sleeping beauty.
伯吉斯吗
Burgess, huh?
专心干活吧你
Just get your head in the game.
好吧  搭档
Okay, pards.
你有多了解这些家伙  慕斯
How well you know these guys, Mouse?
不知道  谁又能真正了解谁呢
I don't know. How well does anybody know anybody, you know?
尽说废话
That's not that helpful.
什么情况
What do we got?
我手上有你要找的东西
You're looking for some stuff I can get for you.
东西
Stuff?
-什么东西  -雷管  导火线
- Like what exactly? - Blasting caps, det cord.
我为什么会需要这些东西呢
Why would I need something like that?
这是你的事  不是吗
Hey, what you do with it is your business, right?
是吗  警探
Really, Detective?
全凭我做主吗
Would it be my business?
警探
Detective?
什么意思  查理
What are you talking about, Charlie?
闭嘴  慕斯
Shut up, Mouse.
我去警署找艾琳·琳德赛时我们见过
We met at the station with Erin Lindsay,
贵人多忘事吗
or did you forget?
不  我没那么健忘
No, I definitely wouldn't forget something like that.
你有什么想跟我交待吗  查理
Is there anything you want to tell us, Charlie?
没有  无话可说
Nope. I'm super cool, man.
帮我跟艾琳打声招呼
Tell Erin I said hey, though.
她以前可真是个尤物
Back in the day, she was, mm, something.
刚才那是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
他不是说了吗  他去找琳德赛时见过我
Just like he said-- I met him with Lindsay.
-我死定了  -别紧张
- I'm so made, man. - Relax.
慕斯  我会罩你的
Mouse, I got you on this.
那好  我们下一步该怎么做
Okay, what's our next play here?
我还没想好
I don't know yet.
芝加哥希望中心
我听到医嘱了
Uh-huh. I heard what the doctor said.
没错  这就是我痊愈的方法
Yes, this is me healing up,
干好本职工作  不干瞪着天花板
doing my job and not staring at the ceiling--
我就喜欢做这两件事
Two things I love to do.
这才让我压力大
This is stressful.
现在跟你吵才让我压力大
Arguing with you right now is stressful.
宝贝
Baby?
你好  娜迪亚
Hey, Nadia.
安东尼奥·道森  我是艾琳的同事
Antonio Dawson-- I work with Erin.
我记得你
Yeah, I remember.
她手头刚好有案子  不能来接你
Well, she's very sorry, but a case jumped off,
所以让我来把你带回警署
so I'm supposed to bring you back to the district.
好吧  我去坐公车
It's cool. I'll take the bus.
你逗我吗
Are you kidding me right now?
别这样
Come on.
这事有点儿奇怪
I mean, it's a little weird.
琳德赛应该来接我的
You know, Lindsay's supposed to be picking me up.
可她不回我短信
She dodges my texts.
现在一个警察出现想让我坐他的车
Now a cop shows up and wants me to get in his car.
上面写的哪里
What address is that?
诊所  就是这儿
The clinic, here.
这是男人还是女人的笔迹
Is that a man's handwriting or a woman's?
女人的
Woman's.
没错
Right.
现在可以上车了吗
Will you please get in the car?
可以
Yeah.
对不起我冲你吼了
Sorry I yelled at you.
谢谢
Thank you.
是因为我的妻子
It's my wife.
21-13  西亚当街601号
21-13, we got a panic alarm tripped
有紧急警报
at 601 West Adams.
21-13  在西亚当街601号
21-13 we got a panic alarm tripped,
有紧急警报
601 West Adams.
收到了吗
Do you copy?
21-13  已收到  正赶往现场
21-13, 10-4, en route!
西亚当街601号有紧急警报
Panic alarm sounded, 601 West Adams.
小姑娘  我不知道你的名字
Honey, I don't know your name.
也不想知道你的名字
I don't want to know your name.
今天过后  咱俩就此别过
But after today, we're through.
绝对的
Oh, you're damn right we are.
这件事至关重要  我们要彻查
This is far too important. We have to pursue this.
当然  你等着听我口令行事
Yeah, well, sit tight until I give the word.
你不能这样
You can't talk to me
拿我当新手来看
like I just joined the unit, man.
我每天都全副武装
I put my vest on every day.
和你一样冲锋陷阵
I get my knuckles dirty every day just like you.
别这样
Come on.
没事  没错
No, right.
你说得对
You're right.
-我会跟艾琳谈谈的  -好
- I'll talk to Erin. - Okay.
查理·普列塞
Charlie Pugliese,
或是不管你叫他什么狗屁名字
or however you say his frickin' name--
你知道他惹上什么麻烦了吗
Do you know what he's into?
怎么了
Why?
刚才一个线人带我去见了他
I just had a C.I. sit me down in front of him.
他参与了建筑工地袭击案
He's involved in the construction-site hit.
需要我怎么帮你  艾琳
What do you need here, Erin?
我能处理
I can handle it.
是吗
Really?
怎么处理
How?
什么时候处理  博伊特就在楼上
When? Voight's upstairs.
-等着我们汇报案件进展  -拖延时间就行
- He's waiting for an update. - Just stall.
我需要先把一些事处理一下
I just need to move a couple things around.
你到底有什么把柄在他手里
What does this guy have on you?
很严重的事
It's bad.
博伊特经常说什么来着
What's Voight always say?
跟他实话实说  他会帮你掩盖
Tell him the truth so he can lie for you.
不  如果这次讲实话  我就完蛋了
No, if I tell the truth on this one, I'm done.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
他们把一个警卫的尸体
There's a dead security guard
扔在垃圾桶后面
that they left behind a dumpster
当一袋垃圾一样
like a bag of trash.
天呐
Oh, man.
我刚才还跟弗里德曼说呢
I was telling Friedman.
明明是他触发了警报  他还不承认
He hit the alarm. He said, "No, I didn't."
我还跟他用一份皮萨诺家的深盘比萨打赌呢
I said, "I'll bet you a Pizano's deep dish you did."
看来他得买单了
Well, he's gonna be paying now.
-所以是假警报  -没错
- So false alarm. - Yeah.
对不起  那个报警按钮应该换个地方
Sorry. They really got to move that alarm button.
这个位置太容易被膝盖碰到了
It's right at knee level.
既然我们到这里了
Well, as long as we're here,
给我来个牛肉香肠套餐
I'll take a beef and sausage combo.
2113报告一起正在进行的抢劫
2113 reporting a robbery in progress,
西亚当斯街601号  请求紧急支援
601 West Adams, requesting immediate backup.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我们出来的时候  我注意到
As we were coming out, I saw the security camera lens
监控摄像头被新喷上了黑漆
had been freshly sprayed with black paint.
我还看到收银抽屉开着  里面是空的
I also saw the cash drawer was open, no tray.
举起手来
Show me your hands.
顺便说一句  我叫伯吉斯
My name is Burgess, by the way.
记不记随你便
Feel free to forget it.
那孩子会安排我们和科普兰·布里格斯见面
The kid here set up an appointment with Copeland Briggs.
是这么回事吗
Let me get this straight.
你们见一个人是为了去见另个一人
You talked to a guy in order to talk to a guy?
警长  科普兰·布里格斯这种人
Sarge, Copeland Briggs--
不是想见就能见的
he comes to you, not the other way around.
是真的  这一趟没白跑
It's true. It was worth a trip.
好吧  那布里格斯能告诉我们什么
All right, so what's Briggs gonna give us?
我听说他私下
Word I got is he provide
给建筑工地提供保护
a little off-the-book security to the construction site.
布里格斯肯定知道谁和抢劫有关
Briggs'll know who's involved in that robbery, for a fact.
去吧
Yeah, go ahead.
霍斯特德的线人呢
What about Halstead's C.I.?
不靠谱
Snake eyes.
你们花了四个小时才发现吗
Took you guys four hours to roll that?
他带我们兜了个大圈子  老大
It was a big runaround, boss.
你理解这种情况吧
You know how it is.
我开始有点理解了
I guess I'm beginning to.
吉恩
Jin...
你查到什么了
What do you got?
我在博伊特办公室安了窃听器
I got ears in Voight's office,
按你的要求
like you wanted.
是吗
You don't say?
琳德赛有情况
It's Lindsay.
她偷偷在找一家珠宝市场的建筑设计图
She was sniffing around for some blueprints to a jewelry mart.
我不知道是什么事
I don't know what it is,
但这是条线索  对吗
but, well, that's something, right?
我需要细节
I need details.
你父亲和他赌博的毛病需要细节
Your father and his gambling problems need details.
我明白
I know.
我不希望移民局找你老爹的麻烦
I don't want immigration involved with your old man,
但是没有细节  我也别无选择
but without details, what choice do I have?
咱们去转一圈
Let's go for a ride.
继续开
Keep driving.
拐弯
Turn.
我不知道你认为我说了或者做了什么
I don't know what you think I might've said or done.
在这里停下
Pull over up here.
你想说什么吗
Something you want to tell me?
显然有些事...
Look, obviously something happened--
你告诉普拉特你在我办公室里
You told Platt you were updating
升级电脑
the computer in my office.
电脑并没有升级
It hasn't been updated.
然后你和内务部的人见面
Then you meet with Internal Affairs.
他们查获了一家地下赌场
They busted up an underground casino
我爸爸欠那赌场的钱
that my dad owes money to.
斯蒂维尔一直用这事要挟我
Stillwell's been using it against me.
谁没被威胁过  吉恩
Everybody gets squeezed, Jin.
你违反了我的第一大原则
You violated my number-one rule.
你为谁工作
Who do you work for?
你
You.
为你
走吧
Come on.
谢谢
Thank you.
你妻子来过电话
Hey. Your wife called.
下一步是找一份工作
So the next step would be finding a job,
一份真正的工作
a real job...
一份让我能抬起头来做人的工作
One that I'm proud of.
-你有打算了吗  -还不算确定
- Do you have any leads? - Well, nothing in stone.
但是在诊所帮忙的一个女的
But there's this woman that helps out at the clinic.
说她能介绍我和她女儿认识
She said she'd introduce me to her daughter,
她女儿开了一家服装店什么的
who runs some sort of clothing store or something.
我不知道  我还得再确认一下
I don't know. I need to work on that one.
太好了
It's all good.
听着  娜迪亚  不许再让我失望了
Listen, Nadia, don't break my heart again.
不会的
I won't.
我保证
I promise.
好
All right.
你待在这里等我下班  好吗
Uh, you're gonna stay up here till I'm off, all right?
可能需要挺长时间
It might be a while,
不过你安定下来之前可以先和我住
but you can stay with me till you get settled.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?
不
Uh, no...
非常不好
not by a long shot.
查理·普列塞
Charlie Pugliese.
怎么了
What now?
当年我完全是一团糟
Back then, I was a mess.
你知道的
You know.
-我以为我爱他  -艾琳
- I thought that I loved him. - Erin...
你那时才16岁
you were 16.
他25岁
He was 25.
他带你吸毒
He got you hooked on dope.
对  这些我都不否认
Yeah. I don't deny any of that.
但当时爸爸被终身监禁
But dad had been locked up forever,
而我妈根本就不回家
and when my mom stopped coming home at all,
是查理一直交供暖费
Charlie kept the heat on.
一直往家里拿食物
He kept food on the table.
那时候我很听他的话
I was loyal to him.
如果只是我自己的错也就算了
And if that's a fault of mine, then so be it.
但是
But, um...
我最好的朋友  安妮
My best friend, Annie--
她也跟查理混在一起  而且
She was mixed up with Charlie too, and...
她所卷入的事...
and she got pulled into some stuff...
比我的要糟糕的多
way worse than me and, um...
你不会有事的
You're gonna be okay.
告诉我到底怎么回事
Just tell me what's going on.
他真的让我们走投无路了
He's got us boxed in real bad...
我和安妮都是
Me and Annie both.
我需要两个干净整洁的白人男子
Well, I'll need a couple clean-cut white guys.
这里有白人男子吗
Got any white guys around?
北美印第安人的一支
我有十六分之一的彻罗基血统  我能算吗
I'm 1/16 Cherokee. Does that disqualify me?
算  你可以
Nah, you're good.
打算怎么做
What's the play?
这小子跟科普兰·布里格斯约了见面
Kid's got a sit-down with Copeland Briggs,
准备套他的话  看他对劫案知道多少
gonna run a game on him, see what he knows about the robbery.
干吧
Hit it.
你有什么收获  兄弟
What do you got, bro?
这些是最近出狱且受过爆破训练的
These are records of anyone with explosives training
所有人员名单
who recently got out of jail.
我在查他们的逮捕记录中
I'm looking for any mentions of water gels
有没有提到过水胶炸药或是爆破引信
or det cords in their arrest records.
很好  继续查
All right, keep looking.
不然你以为我在干什么
What do you think I'm doing?
是因为劳拉
It's Laura.
我跟她说我要回来工作时  她差点气疯了
She nearly flipped when I told her I was coming back to work.
那她希望你做什么
What does she expect you to do?
她想让我调去离她姐姐近的水晶湖
She wants me to move out to Crystal Lake near her sister,
去那里当个副警长什么的
Barney Fife it out there.
她真的经历了太多
Well, she's been through a lot.
你们全家都是
I mean, your whole family has.
我知道
I know.
但是
But...
我明白
I hear you.
我见过你的警探朋友了
I met your detective friend.
我提到你的名字时  他的眼神很特别
He had a look in his eye when I said your name.
我以前见你的男朋友有过那种眼神
I seen that look in your boys' eyes before.
别说了
Don't.
这是你要的设计图
Here's your blueprints.
还有一件事
I need one more thing.
去死吧
Go to hell.
叫一个枪手午夜去汉考克中心放冷枪
Just call in a shooter at the Hancock at midnight.
那样会吸引大量注意力  是吧
That should get a lot of attention, eh?
快好了  艾琳  就快了哦
Almost there, Erin-- 5-yard line.
真是我的乖妹子
That's my girl.
好  伙计们  听好了
All right, players, listen up.
你们俩是西北来的
You two are northwestern kids.
你们每个月在十大名校联盟能卖掉一百磅大麻
You sell 100 pounds of weed every month all over the Big Ten.
十大联盟有十二所学校  谁给解释一下
Of which there are 12 schools. Somebody explain that one.
-别管这么多了  -是的
- Let's just do this. - Exactly.
我会跟布里格斯说为了交换你们的信息
I'm gonna tell Briggs in return for the info on you guys,
我要他把自己知道的
all I want to know is what he knows
关于工地劫案的信息都告诉我  明白吗
about the construction robbery, you feel me?
他们明白了  我在外面等
They feel you. I'll wait outside.
没有问题的话
No doubt.
我们就开始吧
Let's do it.
-你好  兄弟  -什么事
- What's up, dog? - What's going on?
科普兰·布里格斯在哪儿
Where's Copeland Briggs?
我带了几个牛逼的伙计过来
Got some stone-cold wildcats right here.
是啊
Yeah.
我不...
Hey, well, I don't--
我改主意不想干了
I think I changed my mind about this deal.
赶紧的
Now.
你好  布里格斯
What's up, Briggs?
你是谁  这是谁
Who is you? Who is this?
来给你指条财路  兄弟
Here to make you rich, boy.
我已经发财了  伙计  你想都想不到
I'm rich already, homey, in ways you don't even know.
什么事
What's up?
等等  等一下
Hold on. Wait a minute.
瞧  他们是我的伙计
Now, see, these are my homeys, right?
-他们俩都是  -警察
- Now, these are a couple of-- - Cops.
我们都是警察
We're all cops.
你坐了我的椅子  怎么还不起来
I think you're in my chair. Why don't you hop up?
我们想了解一下工地劫案的情况
We'd like to know about the construction-site robbery.
所以呢
And?
-跟你说我有什么好处  -没好处
- What's in it for me? - Nothing.
要不我们让街角那所学校停课
So how about we let the school around the corner get out,
把小鬼们都拉出来
let all the kids file by,
让他们看见警察跟科普兰·布里格斯一起行动
and they can see the cops just kicking it with Copeland Briggs.
之后  我们也许可以拎一打啤酒
Maybe later, we'll get a 12-pack,
拿到你那儿去
bring it by your place,
最好让所有人都知道你是个线人
let everybody know that you're a C.I., at best.
或者你现在就把我们想知道的告诉我们
Or you just tell us what we want right now,
我们三十秒后就从这里消失
and we'll be out of here in 30 seconds.
好吧  伙计
Look, man...
一个叫"红佬"拉德纳的家伙来过这里
Dude named Red Radner stopped by here.
给了我们一些好处
Dropped a bunch of bread off for us
让我们看着建筑工地的门口
to watch the gate at the construction site
然后有一伙白人冲进去洗劫了那个地方
while a bunch of white boys went in there and robbed the place.
我听见了枪声
Now, I heard gunshots,
但不知道有人被杀了
but I ain't know nobody got killed.
我就知道这么多
That's all I know.
阿特沃特  有时候警徽比鬼扯好用多了
Atwater, sometimes the badge is mightier than the B.S.
"红佬"凯文·拉德纳
Kevin "Red" Radner.
在纽约  印第安纳和伊利诺伊州被通缉
He's wanted in New York, Indiana, and Illinois
涉嫌谋杀   武装抢劫和非法交易
for murder, armed robbery, and trafficking.
-贩毒还是...  -卖淫
- Drugs or-- - Girls.
还逃过了强奸指控
Beat a rape charge too.
关注他是因为建筑工地的
We like him for pulling the strings
抢劫案是他牵线搭桥的
on that construction-site robbery.
他行踪不定  但是以前
He's in the wind, but he's had a lot
跟这家伙有很多生意往来
of prior dealings with this guy,
查理·普列塞
Charlie Pugliese.
我们确信普列塞也是"红佬"团伙的一员
We have every reason to believe Pugliese was part of Red's crew.
据线报说
Tip from a C.I. came in,
普列塞想用工地偷来的炸药
said Pugliese's planning on using the explosives stolen from that site
炸北朗代尔的这家珠宝店抢劫
to knock off this jewelry exchange on North Lawndale.
出发吧
We're moving out.
总归要来的
Can't avoid this.
我知道
I know.
各就各位
All right, be ready.
就是现在  行动
All right, that's it. Move in.
手举起来  举起来
Hands up. Keep them up.
-不许动  -不许动
- Don't move! - Freeze!
手举起来
Put your hands up! Get 'em up!
转过去  手举起来
Turn around, get them hands up!
闭嘴  待着别动
Tune down, just stay there,
不许动
don't move.
别看我  看别的地方
Don't look at me. Look away.
手举高
Keep 'em high!
对  看别的地方
Yeah, yeah, look away.
后备箱里有伤人武器吗
Anything in the trunk that could hurt me?
-没有  -大声点
- No. - I don't hear you.
-没有  -车内有爆炸物
- No. - Explosives in the car.
我要举报一起2002年10月12号的谋杀案
I'd like to report a murder from October 12, 2002.
受害者名叫里奇·桑多瓦尔
Victim's name was Ricky Sandoval.
我有全部的线索
I have all the information--
谁杀了他  谁帮着处理的尸体
who killed him and who helped get rid of the body.
把他带去车里
Put him in the car.
-另外两个开口了吗  -都找了律师
- Anything from the other two? - Lawyered up.
好  大家都走吧
All right, everybody clear out.
等等  先让我跟他谈谈
Hang on. I want to talk to him first.
然后想干什么随你
Then you can do whatever you want.
你想按程序来  艾琳
You wanted to go by the book, Erin.
我奉陪
Well, here we are.
你知道桑多瓦尔怎么对安妮的
You know what Sandoval was doing to Annie.
也知道她为什么杀人
You know why she snapped.
说这些太迟了
It's too late for all that.
我给了你一笔勾销的机会
I gave you a chance to keep it buried.
你想昭告天下  没问题
You want to go public about everything, fine.
但你要知道
But just so you know,
我准备说是我杀了桑多瓦尔
I'm gonna say I killed Sandoval--
不让安妮和特拉维斯骨肉分离
keep Annie and Travis together.
你还真是个警察啊
Wow. You really are a cop, aren't you?
看看这吓人的手段
Bluffing your ass off.
有种就试试
Try me.
你让博伊特毫无理由地把我赶出了城
You let Voight run me out of town with nothing.
没有理由
Nothing!
你可是要被他扔进湖里喂鱼的
You were headed for the bottom of the lake.
我求他饶你一命
I begged for your life.
就这一次  活得有意义点吧
Do something with it, for once.
供出拉德纳  跟我们合作
Give us Radner, cooperate fully,
你只要蹲一年牢
and you're out in a year.
在里面戒了毒  当个男人
Clean yourself up on the inside, become a man,
或许你还会是个合格的父亲
and then maybe you can be a dad to your son.
要么扯出桑多瓦尔的事
Or give a statement on Sandoval.
那你和我...
And then you and me--
我们同归于尽
we can go down the tubes together.
你选吧
It's up to you.
我没杀那个保安
I didn't kill that guard.
"红佬"杀的
Red did.
他现在在哪
Where is he now?
在等着拿自己那份分成
He's waiting for his cut of the heist.
他应该打电话找我的
He was gonna call me.
可一直没打来
But he ain't calling now.
他在哪藏身
Where does he flop?
在城里有女朋友吗
Does he have a girl in town?
我听人说他在"后院"的仓库工作
I heard one of the guys say he worked out of a warehouse in B.Y.
可我从没听说过那里
Never heard of that area before.
我猜这12年不少东西都变了
A lot's changed in 12 years, I guess.
"后院"  从来没听过
B.Y.-- I've never heard of it before.
应该没人听过吧
I don't think anyone has.
你们知道吗  我上一份工作
Hey, you know, at my old job,
有时候我们会这么叫屠宰场后面的地方
sometimes we'd get called to this area behind the stockyards.
大家喜欢把车停在那  因为晚上很安静
Guys liked to park there 'cause it was quiet at night.
屠宰场后面  就是"后院"
Back of the yards was B.Y.
我们走
Let's go.
伯吉斯
Hey, Burgess.
警长
Sergeant.
和德兰尼搭档感觉如何
How do you like working with Delaney?
他太软弱了
He's soft.
你自己也跟我说过
And you yourself, you once told me
你不喜欢软弱的警察
that you have no tolerance for soft cops.
知道吗  我也不喜欢
You know what? I don't either.
我想要阿特沃特那样的搭档
I want someone like Atwater,
不怕趟浑水的人
someone who isn't afraid to mix it up.
不然我干嘛要当警察
Otherwise, what the hell am I doing this for?
你说得对  他是很浑
You're right. He's a dog ass.
你被情报组拒绝时
When you got passed over for Intelligence,
我以为你一定会一蹶不振像饼干一样碎掉
I thought for sure you'd crumble like a chocolate-chip cookie.
明天我会让你和高根搭档
So tomorrow I'll put you with Gogan.
他虽然只做了几年警察
He's only a few years on the job,
但是个好警察
but he's good police.
谢了  警长
Thank you, Sergeant.
刚才说的话我一句都不会承认
I'll just deny every word of this conversation.
当然
Of course.
我听说你的事了  干得不错
I heard you had a good bust.
是啊  这都要谢谢你
Yeah, well, thanks to you,
我在不断提高自己的职业素养
I get to keep proving myself as a uniform.
我早就就料到了
I guess I had that coming.
回见
I'll see you later.
这里没什么大问题
It's pretty secure,
金属门  窗户订上了
metal doors, boards on the windows...
都挺普通的
pretty usual.
肯定是这里
This is definitely the place.
有个人刚开了辆货车进来  盯着我看
Guy just pulled in a van, put eyes on me.
-他认出你是警察了吗  -不知道
- Did he make you as police? - I can't tell.
好吧  盯紧那里
All right, keep eyes on the place.
好吧  我想他认出来了
Yeah, I'd say I'm made!
呼叫指挥中心
10-1!
多人枪击警察
Multiple shots fired at the police!
我们受到重火力袭击
We are taking heavy fire!
急需增援
Need immediate backup!
请求特警支援
Requesting S.W.A.T.!
货车来了
Van!
追货车
快点跟上  往旁边开
Go, go, go! Get alongside!
安全  前面我看不到
Clear! I can't clear!
掩护我
Cover back.
不许动  举起手来
Don't move! Show me your hands.
枪  我有枪
Gun! I got a gun!
整理好了吗
Squared away?
好了
Yeah.
整了一堆阴阳资料  但今天可算好了
Paperwork up the yin-yang, but I'm toast for today.
谢谢你
Thank you...
所有的一切
for everything.
这就是搭档的作用
That's why you have backup.
我也觉得
Yeah, I guess so.
汉克
Hank.
我们有很多种合作的方式
There's a lot of ways this relationship can go.
我觉得这是最简单的
I figure this is the easiest.
这是五千美元
It's $5,000.
是我刚从街上收的百分之十
It's 10% of what I just took off the street--
绝对不会被发现
totally untraceable.
删除文件
爸爸
Dad.
你现在去收拾行李
I need you to pack up everything you have, okay?
然后离开芝加哥
And get out of Chicago.
现在就去  爸爸  快去
Go now, Dad. Go.
我再打给你  拜
I'll call you. Bye.
删除成功
亚当
Adam.
我...
I, um...
我是来向你道歉的
I came here to apologize to you.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
So, uh, I'm sorry.
你是个好警察
You're a really good cop,
你肯定很快就能有机会的
and you are gonna get your shot again soon.
你大老远跑来就是和我说这个的
You came all the way here just to tell me that.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我知道你知道的
I know you know that.
我很想你
And I miss you.
有他是我做过唯一正确的事
He's the only good thing I've ever done.
不是的
That's not true.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
你是个好妈妈
You're a good mom.
就一直这样下去吧
Let's leave it at that.
我都不知道如果他被带走了
I don't even know what I would have done
我会做出什么
if he was taken away from me.
你现在不用担心这个
You don't have to think about that now.
那么...
So...
查理
Charlie...
坦白了
Confessed.
可能他会学着合作一点的
He'll probably get a little rhythm for cooperating.
安妮  抱歉
Annie, I'm sorry.
我不该让查理回到你的生活中
I should've never let Charlie back in.
江山易改  本性难移
People don't change.
但你变了
You did.
孩子们
Hey, guys.
爸爸回来了
Dad's home.
劳拉
Laura?
孩子们
Guys?
谢尔顿·吉恩
Sheldon Jin.
他是你们情报组的人吧
I believe he worked in your unit.
是的  正是
Yeah, that's right.